<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Ion Moroșanu</title>
    <link>https://morosanu.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Ion Moroșanu</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 15:52:10 +0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://morosanu.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Adding Comments to My Blog</title>
      <link>https://morosanu.io/posts/adding-comments-to-my-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 15:52:10 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://morosanu.io/posts/adding-comments-to-my-blog/</guid>
      <description>Motivation Being relatively new to the world of blogging, I quickly realized that my recently created website was missing a crucial element – reader feedback. It was evident that I needed to find a way to bridge this gap and encourage readers to voice their opinions and thoughts on my posts.
The Search for a Good Commenting Solution: My website is on GitHub and uses Hugo static site generation. So, I needed a commenting solution that fits this setup.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wordle: A Telegram Bot Game in Go</title>
      <link>https://morosanu.io/posts/wordle-game-telegram-bot/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 15:20:39 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://morosanu.io/posts/wordle-game-telegram-bot/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Being mainly a Java programmer, I decided however to expand my area of knowledge and the fates fell on the Go language. And the best way to learn is to apply, to practice what you learn! I usually prefer to do this by implementing a game or a tool that has some use.
So this time it&amp;rsquo;s a game - Wordle, but implemented as a Telegram Bot.
Environment To run Go code, you need to install Go on your local computer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World! A Glimpse into the World of a Seasoned Software Engineer</title>
      <link>https://morosanu.io/posts/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 12:55:32 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://morosanu.io/posts/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Hello, world! It&amp;rsquo;s a pleasure to embark on this blogging journey and share my experiences as a software engineer with all of you. With over 15 years of expertise in the realms of C, Python, and Java, my journey has primarily revolved around backend development. However, I have recently set my sights on the captivating realm of modern frontend technologies. In this blog post, I&amp;rsquo;ll take you through my transition, the challenges I&amp;rsquo;ve encountered, and the excitement of expanding my skill set to include the modern frontend stack.</description>
    </item>
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
